Do you know the term "cloud computing"?
What is cloud computing?
A data center at the end of the Internet
The term "cloud computing" refers to a system
0:00:08.110,0:00:12.420.
This is a term that refers to the type of system in which a user performs some task
0:00:12.420,0:00:17.070 When a user performs some task, the computer in front of him or her or the company
It's not a server on the network.
Using a server on the Internet
In other words, we use a server on the Internet, not a server on the network, to perform the processing.
From corporate business applications to personal applications
to those of
This is called cloud computing.
A number of services have emerged.
Recently, word processing and spreadsheet
Office applications that used to be available on a PC
Office applications are also coming out.
Translated with www.DeepL.com/Translator (free version)